Gomez

Line Chef

CONTACT



G gh-gomezzzer

in linkedin-Jorge-Gomez-a6865313a

SKILLS

Knife Skills, Time management, Butchery, Food safety, HTML, CSS, GitHub, VS Code...

EDUCATION

General

Austin Community College 2010-2011

Front-end Web Development Techdegree

Treehouse Coding 2021-2022

ABOUT

Greetings, My name is Jorge Gomez. I have been in the restaurant industry for 17 years. I started my culinary venture at a French Brasserie in 2002, outside of Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Working my way up from Grade Manger to Chef de partie/Grill. I fell in love with French technique and approach to cooking, working for a seasoned French Chef named Jean Maurice Juge. I have sinced worked with many different types of cusine such as Italian, Japanese, Vietnamese, and modern American.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Line Cook

Revolution BrewPub | 2021 - 2022 Executing BrewPub style cuisine in a timely manner

- Working clean, clean as you go approach
 Communication skills
- Staying busy
- Lead Cook/Yaki Grill Cook

Kome | 2020

Grill, Saute, Fry stations. Japanese street food

- · Was a candidate for Sous in 2 months
- · Lead team in an efficient dinner service

Lead Line Cook

CookBook Cafe/Austin Public Library | 2019

Opening Lead Cook, checking orders,

- Delegating prep to line Cooks and Prep Cooks
 Organizing hot line
 Scratch Kitchen

Line Cook

Flower Child | 2017 - 2018 Line and Prep cook, Wok Station

- Executing lunch service for 200 people a day
 Maintaining a clean work station
 Keeping station stocked and rotated

Sous Chef/ Lead Cook

Buenos Aires Cafe | 2015 - 2017 Running the day to day operations, assisting the Executive Chef

- Argentinian scratch kitchen, menu development, daily specials, recipes
 Meat butchery and portion control
 Training and managing employees